Lucky Jain

Software Engineer

Phase 2, Haripura Vidisha, MP 464001 +91 7247064715 luckyjain7247@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Full Stack web developer specializing in React js, Node js, and JavaScript. I provide effective solutions from both the frontend and the backend side. I have helped corporations further their growth by creating smooth, attractive and interactive Web Applications with my skills. I am an enthusiastic, productive, highly energetic and a skillful programmer who is always open to learn new technologies and find opportunities to grow.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS. JavaScript, React JS, Node JS, REST APIs, Next JS, Redux, Tailwind CSS, Material UI, SaSS, Git, JSON, Frontend Development, Full Stack Development

EXPERIENCE

LeadSquared, Bangalore (KT)- Software Engineer - Integration SEP 2022- PRESENT

Six30 Labs, Bangalore (KT)- SDE 1

MAY 2022- SEP 2022

Six30 Labs, Bangalore (KT)- SDE 1 intern

FEBRUARY 2022 - MAY 2022

EDUCATION

St Mary's PG College, Vidisha (MP)- *B.Sc. (Computer Science)*

June 2018 - September 2021.

PROJECTS

Full Stack Blog Application

JULY 2022

• MERN Stack application. Image upload, Login, Register, CRUD operations. Use of Context API for state management. Attractive UI using Bootstrap 5.

Next JS Instagram Clone

MAY 2022

• Next JS, Tailwind CSS, Next-Auth, Firebase. Add a post, like-comment, image upload.

Google Keep Clone

APR 2022

• MERN Stack application. Login, Register, CRUD operations. Use of Context API for state management. Attractive UI with exact theme as Google Keep, built using Bootstrap 5.